Guide to the David M. Kennedy Papers SC1115
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Teaching, Series 3
  - Modern America - S.I.W. 1998 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - History 53F - Freshman Seminar "Reflections on American Cond." (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - History 165C-1995 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Grad. Seminar: 1991-92 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Mod. Am. - Aut. 92 - Hist. 258 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - History 3, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - MLA Program (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - History 266s - research seminar on U.S. foreign relations, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - History 351e - "Joint Graduate Colloquium", 1988 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Graduate Seminar, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- Travel, Series 4
  - AHA, 2004 Jan (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Angels Seminar (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Berlin, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Australia, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Fish, Cancun, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Danube, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Cancun/Cuba (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Judy's Danube (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - D.N.C. - L.A., 2000 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - England-France, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Fargo, 2003 Oct (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Firenze, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Germany, 1994 Feb (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Gold Spike Celebration, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Gold Spike Celebration, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Italy, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Italy, 1994 Mar (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Italy, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Italy, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Lakeside Talk (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Mexico (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Montana - "Off Beaten Path" (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Contemporary Political History Conference (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Centennial, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Computer Files, Series 5
  - Various Floppy Disks (Box 38)
- Birth Control in America: The Career of Margaret Sanger manuscript and research material, 1914-1968; Accession ARCH-2015-054
  - PhD Dissertation: Birth control: its heroine + its history in America part 1, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - PhD Dissertation: Birth control: its heroine + its history in America part 2, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - PhD Dissertation: Birth control: its heroine + its history in America part 3, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - MSS: The Woman Rebel Ch. 1 part 1, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - MSS: The Woman Rebel Ch. 1 part 2, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Woman Rebel Background, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - MSS Ch. 3: Maragaret Sanger + the Birth Control Movement, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - MSS Ch. 4, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - MSS Ch. 4, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - MSS Ch. 5, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - MSS Ch. 6, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - MSS Ch. 7, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - MSS Ch. 9, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Birth Control Bibliography, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Birth Control Dissertation Notes, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Birth Control Congressional Campaign, 1931-35 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - American Birth Control League CABCL, 1925-38 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Birth Control - Foreign, 1935-1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Birth Control History, 1936-46 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Contraception - Legal part 1, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Contraception - Legal part 2, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Contraception - Legal part 3, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Birth Control Medical + Social, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Birth Control - Morality, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Birth Control - Propaganda, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Birth Control - Publications, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Birth Control - Public Health, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Birth Control - Technique, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Birth Control Review, 1920-1930 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Blossom Affair, 1921-1922 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - News from Margaret Sanger, 1936-1932 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Margaret Sanger Biographical, 0 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2017-071
  - Birth Control - Foreign (Library of Congress), undated; 1.1; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 1)
  - Baruch & Raymond Fosdick (Princeton), undated; 1.2; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 1)
  - Selected Documents from the Papers of Franklin D. Roosevelt Concerning Generoso Pope, undated; 1.3; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 1)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2017-326
  - American Issues Radio Forum, 1976 Apr 3; 1_01; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - American Issues Radio Forum #9, 1976 Apr 3; 1_02; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - American Issues Radio Forum, 1976 Apr 3; 1_03; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - American Issues Radio Forum #3, 1976 Apr 3; 1_04; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - American Issues Radio Forum Seg. 1-3, 1976 Apr 3; 1_05; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - American Issues Radio Forum #4, 1976 Apr 3; 1_06; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)